Guide to the Communist Party of the United States of America Audio Collection TAM.132.001
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archive
- Series IV: Audio Cassette Tapes: Public Events
  - Subseries IV:A: Events
    - Herbert Aptheker, Lecture on W. E. B. Du Bois. San Francisco, CA, Feb 18, 1968 (Box 38, Cassette 2774)
    - Ho Chi Minh Memorial, [1969] (Box 32, Cassette 4889)
    - Peace and Freedom Party Convention. Includes Ossie Davis, Nathan Schwerner, Fannie Lou Hamer and Grace Mora Newman, Jun 1, 1968 - Jun 2, 1968 (Box 30, Cassette 1502)
    - Students for a Democratic Society, National Convention. Panel on Racism, Jun 19, 1969 (Box 28, Cassette 1137)
    - [Anti-Vietnam War] Rally. Grant Park, Chicago, IL, Aug 1969 (Box 58, Cassette 1140)
    - Gus Hall, City Club Forum. Cleveland, OH, Oct 10, 1969 (Box 38, Cassette 2775)
    - Fred Hampton, Testimony on Police Violence. Tape 2, Nov 1969 (Box 58, Cassette 1138)
    - Henry Winston, Speech on Anti-Imperialism, 1970 (Box 59, Cassette 997)
    - OBA Convention. Voting on Resolutions. Tape 7, 1970 (Box 32, Cassette 4847)
    - Huey P. Newton, Lecture. Chicago, IL, [1970 - 1972] (Box 58, Cassette 1194)
    - Gus Hall, Leninism and Internationalism, New York, NY, Jan 21, 1970 (Box 38, Cassette 2780)
    - Bobby Seale, Message to "R & F" Conference. Tape 5 (?), Jan 27, 1970 (Box 38, Cassette 2804)
    - Charlene Mitchell, Lenin, the State and Repression. Center for Marxist Education, New York, NY. Lecture 5. [Condition poor: creation of user copy may pose problems. Contact tamiment.wagner@nyu.edu], Mar 18, 1970 (Box 58, Cassette 1147)
    - James Jackson, Lenin and National Liberation. Center for Marxist Education, New York, NY. Lecture 6, Apr 1, 1970 (Box 58, Cassette 1149)
    - Daniel Rubin, Lenin and the Revolutionary Party. Center for Marxist Education, New York, NY. Lecture 7, Apr 15, 1970 (Box 58, Cassette 1148)
    - Gus Hall, and [Frances?] Gabow, Press Conference. "Black Palmer House", Aug 1970 (Box 38, Cassette 2805)
    - N.E.T. Journal, Hiroshima and Nagasaki, Aug 1970 (Box 59, Cassette 1052)
    - Gus Hall, The Full Potential of this Moment. Seattle, WA, Aug 5, 1970 (Box 38, Cassette 2777)
    - [Roscoe] Procter and [James] Haughton, Lectures. Marxist Center, NY. Tape 1, Nov 1970 (Box 58, Cassette 1207)
    - [Roscoe] Procter and [James] Haughton, Lectures. Marxist Center, NY. Tape 2, Nov 1970 (Box 58, Cassette 1205)
    - People's Forum. Henry Winston, Speech. Boston, MA, Nov 15, 1970 (Box 59, Cassette 998)
    - Gus Hall, 60th Birthday Banquet. Chicago, IL, Dec 3, 1970 (Box 38, Cassette 2776)
    - Gus Hall Dinner. Includes Singing, Dec 6, 1970 (Box 38, Cassette 2806)
    - Angela Davis, Interview with Margaret Burnham. New York Women's House of Detention, New York, NY, Dec 17, 1970 (Box 32, Cassette 4919)
    - Angela Must Be Free. Includes Celia Zitron, F. D. Kirkpatrick, Fania Jordan, Robert Neves, Edith Segal, [1971 or 1972] (Box 52, Cassette 3968)
    - Herbert Aptheker, Press Conference on the Middle East Crisis, Jan 15, 1971 (Box 32, Cassette 4945)
    - Herbert Aptheker, Lecture on the Middle East Crisis, Jan 24, 1971 (Box 38, Cassette 2807)
    - Jarvis Tyner, United Front against Fascism, Jan 31, 1971 (Box 38, Cassette 2808)
    - Judy Edelman, Working Class and Industrial Concentration, Feb 1, 1971 (Box 38, Cassette 2809)
    - Michael Zagarell, Centrality of the Peace Struggle and Peaceful Coexistence, Feb 2, 1971 (Box 38, Cassette 2810)
    - Jarvis Tyner, Black Liberation and the Roots of Black Oppression, Feb 3, 1971 (Box 38, Cassette 2812)
    - Judy Edelman, The Woman Question and the Role of the Young Workers Liberation League in the Fight against Male Supremacy, Feb 3, 1971 (Box 38, Cassette 2811)
    - Angela Davis Defense Discussion. Judy Edelman, Opening Remarks, Feb 4, 1971 (Box 38, Cassette 2813)
    - Jarvis Tyner, History of Youth Work and Party-League Relations. Tape 1, Feb 5, 1971 (Box 38, Cassette 2814)
    - Jarvis Tyner, Party-League Relations. Tape 2, Feb 5, 1971 (Box 38, Cassette 2815)
    - Gus Hall, Struggle against White Chauvinism and Racism, Mar 1971 (Box 38, Cassette 2817)
    - Rasheed [Storey], Discussion, S.C. Racism, Mar 27, 1971 (Box 35, Cassette 3012)
    - Henry Winston, Lecture. Patrice Lumumba University (Peoples' Friendship University), Moscow, Mar 31, 1971 (Box 59, Cassette 969)
    - Joe Brandt, Report on AKFIC. Pyongyang, North Korea. Tape 1, May 1971 (Box 38, Cassette 2778)
    - Joe Brandt, Report on AKFIC. Pyongyang, North Korea. Tape 2, May 1971 (Box 38, Cassette 2779)
    - Henry Winston, May Day Speech. Los Angeles, CA, May 1, 1971 (Box 38, Cassette 2818)
    - David Poindexter, Lecture, May 28, 1971 (Box 58, Cassette 1181)
    - Henry Winston, Party Building and Discussion, Jul 16, 1971 (Box 38, Cassette 2820)
    - Richard Nixon, on the Economy / Robert West, on Unitarians, Aug 14, 1971 (Box 58, Cassette 1164)
    - Henry Winston, Pan-Africanism, Sep 1, 1971 (Box 59, Cassette 1078)
    - Unidentified Rally. Includes Arthur [?], Louise Patterson, and Mrs. Davis. Central Park, New York, NY, Sep 25, 1971 (Box 64, Cd 1280 (disks 1-2), Box 58, Cassette 1280)
    - Rally against the Vietnam War. Chicago, IL. Tape 1, Oct 13, 1971 (Box 58, Cassette 1177)
    - Rally against the Vietnam War. Chicago, IL. Tape 2, Oct 13, 1971 (Box 58, Cassette 1173)
    - Racism and Prisons. [Condition poor: creation of user copy may pose problems. Contact tamiment.wagner@nyu.edu], 1972 (Box 58, Cassette 1172)
    - Gus Hall - Jarvis Tyner Election Campaign, 1972 (Box 38, Cassette 2821)
    - Unidentified Conference. Arnold Johnson, Lecture. Tape 1, 1972 (Box 55, Cassette 4174)
    - Unidentified Conference. Arnold Johnson, Lecture. Tape 2, 1972 (Box 55, Cassette 4175)
    - Gus Hall - Jarvis Tyner Election Campaign, [1972 or 1976] (Box 52, Cassette 4027)
    - Henry Winston, Speech. Unidentified School, Soviet Union, Jan 4, 1972 (Box 59, Cassette 1056)
    - Welfare Rights, Mar 1972 (Box 58, Cassette 1183)
    - Fania Davis Jordan, on the Defense of Angela Davis. Introduced by Antioch Instructor Harold Rodgers. Antioch University, Yellow Springs, OH. [Condition poor: creation of user copy may pose problems. Contact tamiment.wagner@nyu.edu], Apr 1972 (Box 58, Cassette 1215)
    - Fania Davis Jordan, on the Defense of Angela Davis. Malcolm X College, Chicago, IL, Apr 29, 1972 (Box 58, Cassette 1222)
    - Angela Davis Rally. Includes Kermin Colemand and Willy Barry, Apr 29, 1972 (Box 38, Cassette 2863)
    - Angela Davis, Speech. Chicago, IL, Jun 16, 1972 (Box 38, Cassette 2823)
    - Angela Davis, Speech. Chicago, IL and Detroit, MI, Jun 16, 1972; Jun 18, 1972 (Box 58, Cassette 1161)
    - Angela Davis, Speech. Detroit, MI, Jun 18, 1972 (Box 38, Cassette 2824)
    - Gus Hall, Meeting, Jun 18, 1972 (Box 38, Cassette 2825)
    - Gus Hall, on the Victory of the Communist Party of Illinois, Jun 18, 1972 (Box 38, Cassette 2826)
    - Gus Hall, Recruitment Meeting. Hotel Diplomat, Jun 27, 1972 (Box 38, Cassette 2827)
    - Democratic National Convention. George McGovern, Acceptance Speech. Also Includes [James?] Jackson, [Jul] 1972 (Box 58, Cassette 1144)
    - Trade Union Action and Democracy (TUAD). Elections Conference. Reports, Jul 1, 1972 (Box 28, Cassette 1227)
    - Gus Hall Election Campaign Interview. University of Minnesota, Minneapolis, MN, Sep, 1972 (Box 38, Cassette 2822)
    - Henry Winston, Committee for a Just Peace in the Middle East. Tape 1, Sep 27, 1972 (Box 38, Cassette 2828)
    - Henry Winston, Committee for a Just Peace in the Middle East. Tape 2, Sep 27, 1972 (Box 38, Cassette 2829)
    - Gus Hall, Speech. Morgantown, WV, Sep 28, 1972 (Box 58, Cassette 1239)
    - Soviet-American Students. Hamilton College, Clinton, NY. [Tape 1?], Nov 1972 (Box 38, Cassette 2830)
    - Soviet-American Students. Hamilton College, Clinton, NY. Tape 2, Nov 1972 (Box 32, Cassette 4954)
    - On the Nagorno-Karabakh Autonomous District, Soviet Union, Dec 13, 1972 (Box 58, Cassette 1268)
    - Lecture, [On Unidentified Work Stoppage and Union Drive]. Washington Heights, NY, [1973] (Box 58, Cassette 1259)
    - Industrial Concentration Conference. Judy Edelman, Opening and Main Report. Tape 1, Jan 1973 (Box 34, Cassette 1654)
    - Industrial Concentration Conference. Judy Edelman, Report. Tape 2, [Jan 1973] (Box 34, Cassette 1655)
    - Industrial Concentration Conference. Committee Reports, [Judy Edelman?]. Tape 7, Jan 1973 (Box 34, Cassette 1613)
    - Industrial Concentration Conference. Building the Young Workers Liberation League Workshop. Tape 8, [Jan 1973] (Box 34, Cassette 1611)
    - Industrial Concentration Conference. Building the Young Workers Liberation League Workshop. Jarvis Tyner and Judy Edelman, Meaning of Labral's Assassination and Summary. [Condition poor: creation of user copy may pose problems. Contact tamiment.wagner@nyu.edu], Jan 1973 (Box 34, Cassette 1612)
    - Gus Hall, Comments. Chicago, IL. Tape 1, Jan 13, 1973 (Box 55, Cassette 4178)
    - Henry Winston, National Question and Full-Time School. Tape 1, Mar 5, 1973 (Box 59, Cassette 992)
    - Henry Winston, National Question. Tape 2, Mar 5, 1973 (Box 59, Cassette 991)
    - Victoria [Stevens?], Student Report, Main Conference, Mar 16, 1973 - Mar 17, 1973 (Box 38, Cassette 2831)
    - John Pittman, United Nations and Peaceful Coexistence / Unidentified Lecture, Mar 17, 1973; Mar 22, 1973 (Box 59, Cassette 861)
    - Hyman Lumer, Zionism, Mar 20, 1973 (Box 38, Cassette 2832)
    - Hyman Lumer, Zionism / William Weinstone, Party History, Mar 20, 1973 (Box 38, Cassette 2833)
    - William Weinstone, Party History, Mar 20, 1973 (Box 38, Cassette 2834)
    - National Training School. Daniel Rubin, Mar 30, 1973 (Box 38, Cassette 2835)
    - National Training School. Daniel Rubin, Lecture on Anti-Monopoly Coalition and Class Discussion, Mar 29, 1973 - Mar 30, 1973 (Box 38, Cassette 2841)
    - National Training School. Daniel Rubin, Anti-Monopoly Coalition Class Discussion, Mar 30, 1973 (Box 38, Cassette 2836)
    - National Training School. Daniel Rubin (2nd Day, Morning), Mar 30, 1973 (Box 38, Cassette 2838)
    - National Training School. Daniel Rubin (2nd Day, Morning and Afternoon), Mar 30, 1973 (Box 38, Cassette 2837)
    - National Training School. Daniel Rubin (3rd Day, Morning), Mar 31, 1973 (Box 38, Cassette 2840)
    - National Training School. Daniel Rubin (3rd Day, Afternoon), Mar 30, 1973 (Box 38, Cassette 2839)
    - Stevens and Black, Estimates. Washington, DC. Tape 2, Apr 19, 1973 (Box 58, Cassette 1127)
    - Henry Winston, May Day Speech. Includes Dave Woody. Los Angeles, CA, Apr 29, 1973 (Box 59, Cassette 1029)
    - Richard Nixon, Speech, Apr 30, 1973 (Box 58, Cassette 1200)
    - Michael Zagarell, Cadre Training Introduction / Jarvis Tyner, Role of the League. Tape 1, May 1973 (Box 38, Cassette 2842)
    - Jarvis Tyner, Role of the League / [Shelby] Richardson, Youth Rights Campaign. Tape 2, May 1973 (Box 38, Cassette 2843)
    - [Shelby] Richardson, Youth Rights Campaign / Michael Zagarell, Struggle against Racism. Tape 3, May 1973 (Box 38, Cassette 2844)
    - Michael Zagarell, Struggle against Racism / Jane Fonda, On North Vietnam. Tape 4, May 1973 (Box 38, Cassette 2845)
    - Henry Winston and Lorenzo [Torrez?], Lectures. University of San Diego (?), CA, May 3, 1973 (Box 59, Cassette 972)
    - People's World Benefit, 35th. Includes Henry Winston. Oakland, CA, May 6, 1973 (Box 59, Cassette 1085)
    - People's World Benefit, 35th. Includes Bert Corona and Angela Davis. Oakland, CA, May 6, 1973 (Box 58, Cassette 1131)
    - West Coast Commission. Mickey's Report on the People's World, May 10, 1973 (Box 58, Cassette 1151)
    - Unidentified Report from Panel Discussion, Discussion of Proposals, May 12, 1973 (Box 38, Cassette 2848)
    - Unidentified Opening Discussion, May 13, 1973 (Box 38, Cassette 2847)
    - Sylvia Woods, on Trip to Cuba, May 31, 1973 (Box 64, Cd 1263, Box 58, Cassette 1263)
    - James E. Jackson, Watergate, Coexistence, and Brezhnev's visit, Jun 1, 1973 (Box 49, Cassette 5016)
    - Michael Zagarell, What is the League, What are Youth?, Jun 30, 1973 (Box 38, Cassette 2846)
    - Gus Hall, Lecture (edited). Chicago, IL, Jun 30, 1973 (Box 38, Cassette 2849)
    - Gus Hall, Watergate and the Brezhnev Visit. Midland Hotel, Chicago, IL, Jun 30, 1973 (Box 32, Cassette 4939)
    - Victoria Stevens, Class on Youth Rights Campaign, Jul 3, 1973 (Box 38, Cassette 2850)
    - Victoria Stevens, Class on Youth Rights Campaign. [Tape 2?], Jul 3, 1973 (Box 55, Cassette 4167)
    - Michael Zagarell, Struggle against Racism. Tape 1, Jul 5, 1973 (Box 38, Cassette 2851)
    - Michael Zagarell, Struggle against Racism. Tape 2, Jul 5, 1973 (Box 38, Cassette 2852)
    - Discussion, The Fight against Racism. Includes Henry Winston. Philadelphia, PA (?). Tape 2, Jul 28 or Sep 28, 1973 (Box 59, Cassette 1060)
    - Discussion, The Fight against Racism. Includes Henry Winston. Philadelphia, PA (?). Tape 3. [Condition poor: creation of user copy may pose problems. Contact tamiment.wagner@nyu.edu], Jul 28 or Sep 28, 1973 (Box 59, Cassette 978)
    - Communist Party of Chile. Ernesto Ottone, Statement of Thanks for Actions of Solidarity in the United States, Aug 26, 1973 (Box 32, Cassette 4952)
    - Claude Lightfoot, on Africa, Sep 1973 (Box 58, Cassette 1185)
    - Gus Hall, on the Economy, Sep 1973 (Box 38, Cassette 2853)
    - Leonard F. Woodcock (UAW President) and George Meany (AFL-CIO President). [Condition poor: creation of user copy may pose problems. Contact tamiment.wagner@nyu.edu], Sep 2, 1973 (Box 58, Cassette 1251)
    - Salvador Allende, Last Speech, [Sep 11, 1973] (Box 55, Cassette 4179)
    - Salvador Allende, Last Speech and Quilapayon, [Sep 11, 1973] (Box 32, Cassette 4953)
    - Henry Winston, on Chile and US Racism, Sep 15, 1973 (Box 59, Cassette 1033)
    - Conference Preparations Meeting. Tape 1, Oct 5, 1973 (Box 28, Cassette 1125)
    - Conference Preparations Meeting. Tape 2, Oct 5, 1973 (Box 28, Cassette 1126)
    - Conference Preparations Meeting. Tape 3, Oct 5, 1973 (Box 28, Cassette 1122)
    - National Anti-Imperialist Movement in Solidarity with African Liberation (NAIMSAL) Founding Convention. Anthony [Monteiro], Opening Report and Questions. Chicago, IL, Oct 24, 1973 (Box 38, Cassette 2854)
    - National Anti-Imperialist Movement in Solidarity with African Liberation (NAIMSAL) Founding Convention. Includes Henry Winston. Chicago, IL, Oct 24, 1973 (Box 28, Cassette 1406)
    - National Anti-Imperialist Movement in Solidarity with African Liberation (NAIMSAL) Founding Convention. Includes Henry Winston, Introduced by Gus Hall. Chicago, IL, Oct 24, 1973 (Box 44, Cassette 2579)
    - National Anti-Imperialist Movement in Solidarity with African Liberation (NAIMSAL) Founding Convention. Includes Gus Hall and Henry Winston. Chicago, IL, Oct 24, 1973 (Box 38, Cassette 2855)
    - Jewish Affairs Dinner. Henry Winston, Lecture, Dec 16, 1973 (Box 38, Cassette 2856)
    - Salvador Allende Rally, Dec 16, 1973 (Box 58, Cassette 1178)
    - Cuban Solidarity with Chile. Tape 1, 1974 (Box 64, Cd 1179 (2 disks), Box 58, Cassette 1179)
    - Cuban Solidarity with Chile. Tape 2, 1974 (Box 64, Cd 1180 (2 disks), Box 58, Cassette 1180)
    - Henry Winston, Lecture on Abraham Lincoln, the Unity of Working Men and the Russian Revolution, 1974 (Box 59, Cassette 1076)
    - Jesús Colón Memorial. Includes Henry Winston and Alberto Moreau, [1974] (Box 52, Cassette 3985)
    - [National] School Lecture. [Joseph] Brandt, On Maoism and China, 1974 (Box 38, Cassette 2861)
    - Rally [On Inflation], [1974 or 1975] (Box 58, Cassette 1158)
    - [?] Kimmelman, Report on Vietnam, Feb 1, 1974 (Box 38, Cassette 2862)
    - Unidentified Seminar. Includes Louise Patterson, Fred Carrier, Leon Johnson, Herbert Aptheker. Tape 1, Feb 5, 1974 (Box 64, Cd 2857, Box 38, Cassette 2857)
    - Unidentified Seminar. Herbert Aptheker and Question Period. Tape 2, Feb 5, 1974 (Box 38, Cassette 2858)
    - Unidentified Seminar. Question Period. Tape 3, Feb 5, 1974 (Box 38, Cassette 2859)
    - Draft Letter to Don Warner on Motor Controls, Feb 8, 1974 (?) (Box 58, Cassette 1165)
    - International Women's Day. [Condition poor: creation of user copy may pose problems. Contact tamiment.wagner@nyu.edu], Mar 9, 1974 (Box 58, Cassette 1193)
    - Impeachment Rally. Washington, DC. Tape 1, Apr 24, 1974 (Box 58, Cassette 1163)
    - Impeachment Rally. Washington, DC. Tape 2, Apr 24, 1974 (Box 58, Cassette 1162)
    - Judge Bruce Wright and Eleanor Holmes Norton, Hearing on Closing the Tombs, Apr 25, 1974 (Box 58, Cassette 1121)
    - March on Raleigh and Speech on Prisons. Raleigh, NC. [Condition poor: creation of user copy may pose problems. Contact tamiment.wagner@nyu.edu], Jul 4, 1974 (Box 58, Cassette 1261)
    - Rally, National Alliance against Racist and Political Repression. Includes Francine Chavis. Raleigh, NC, Jul 6, 1974 (Box 58, Cassette 1231)
    - Reminiscences and Discussion. Kansas City, KS, Jul 27, 1974 (Box 58, Cassette 1255)
    - Michael Welch, Party Organization, Aug 9, 1974 (Box 38, Cassette 2864)
    - Lecture on the Ethiopian Revolution, Sep 12, 1974 (Box 59, Cassette 1101)
    - Gus Hall, Lecture, Oct 30, 1974 (Box 38, Cassette 2860)
    - Rally on Inflation. [Condition poor: creation of user copy may pose problems. Contact tamiment.wagner@nyu.edu], Nov 1, 1974 (Box 58, Cassette 1198)
    - Rally to Protest Ranaway Prices. Bryant Park, New York, NY. Tape 1, Nov 16, 1974 (Box 32, Cassette 4831)
    - Rally to Protest Ranaway Prices. Bryant Park, New York, NY. Tape 2, Nov 16, 1974 (Box 32, Cassette 4832)
    - Interviews with Sandy Patrinos and Amadeo Richardson about Conrad Komorowski, Jan 8, 1975; Jan 23, 1975 (Box 32, Cassette 5011)
    - Conference [on Peace and Socialism], World Marxist Review. Henry Winston, Address. [Condition poor: creation of user copy may pose problems. Contact tamiment.wagner@nyu.edu], Jan 9, 1974 (Box 59, Cassette 1035)
    - James Jackson, Revolutionary Conditions, Jan 16, 1975 (Box 35, Cassette 2874)
    - National Party School. Elsie Dickson, Lecture. [Condition poor: creation of user copy may pose problems. Contact tamiment.wagner@nyu.edu], Feb 28, 1975 (Box 58, Cassette 1241)
    - National Party School. Sylvia N. and Alva Buxenbaum, Racism. Tape 2, Mar 4, 1975 (Box 35, Cassette 2875)
    - National Party School. Daniel Rubin, Inflation and Women's Equality, Mar 11, 1975 (Box 59, Cassette 923)
    - Jay Schaffner, Youth Question and Male Supremacy. Tape 2, Mar 12, 1975 (Box 59, Cassette 955)
    - National Party School. Matty Berkelhammer, The Youth Question, Mar 13, 1975 (Box 35, Cassette 2876)
    - Carl Winter, Party History (Organizing Unemployed Councils), Mar 17, 1975 (Box 58, Cassette 1395)
    - Carl Winter, Party History (continued). Tape 3, Mar 17, 1975 (Box 35, Cassette 2877)
    - National Party School. Sylvia Newcomb, Party Theory, Mar 19, 1975 - Mar 20, 1975 (Box 59, Cassette 965)
    - National Party School. Henry Winston, Party Theory. Tape 3, Mar 19, 1975 - Mar 20, 1975 (Box 59, Cassette 1096)
    - National Party School. Henry Winston, Party Theory. Tape 4, Mar 19, 1975 - Mar 20, 1975 (Box 59, Cassette 1094)
    - National Party School. Henry Winston, [Party Theory] / Michael [Zagarell], Maoism, Mar 19, 1975 - Mar 20, 1975 (Box 59, Cassette 1097)
    - Michael Zagarell, on Maoism. Tape 2, Mar 20, 1975 (Box 32, Cassette 4905)
    - National Party School. Richard Hoxen, Asian-Americans, Mar 25, 1975 (Box 58, Cassette 1157)
    - Herbert Aptheker, Forum on [Robert] Fogel and [Stanley] Engerman, Apr 18, 1975 (Box 35, Cassette 2878)
    - Vicky Missich, Interview on Experiences with Agent John Beaudin (Durham Tabel), May 28,1975 (Box 32, Folder 5006)
    - Press Conference, TV and Newspaper Interviews. University of Illinois, Urbana and Decatur, IL, Sep 25, 1975 (Box 59, Cassette 1069)
    - Herbert Aptheker, Lecture on the History of People in the United States - The Revolution. Lecture 1 of 7, Oct 10, 1975 (Box 32, Cassette 4940)
    - Unidentified Discussion and Lecture, [Differences between North and South], Oct 17, 1975 (Box 59, Cassette 1006)
    - Herbert Aptheker. Tape 4, Oct 31, 1975 (Box 35, Cassette 2879)
    - Gil Green, on Portugal. University of Northern Iowa, Cedar Falls, IA, Nov 24, 1975 (Box 35, Cassette 2880)
    - Young Workers Liberation League Conference on Jobs. Detroit, MI., Dec 6, 1975 (Box 34, Cassette 1693)
    - Young Workers Liberation League Conference on Jobs. James Steele, Report. Detroit, MI. Tape 2, Dec 6, 1975 (Box 34, Cassette 1691)
    - Young Workers Liberation League Conference on Jobs. Detroit, MI. Tape 3, Dec 6, 1975 (Box 34, Cassette 1692)
    - Young Workers Liberation League Conference on Jobs. Detroit, MI. Tape 4, Dec 6, 1975 (Box 34, Cassette 1694)
    - Young Workers Liberation League Conference on Jobs. Detriot, MI. Tape 5, Dec 6, 1975 (Box 34, Cassette 1695)
    - Young Workers Liberation League Conference on Jobs. James Steele, Summary. Detroit, MI, Dec 6, 1975 (Box 34, Cassette 1690)
    - Young Workers Liberation League Conference on Jobs. Session 4, Report Backs. James Steele, Summary. Detriot, MI, Dec 7, 1975 (Box 34, Cassette 1697)
    - Young Workers Liberation League Conference on Jobs. New York Report and Tommy Dennis. Detroit, MI. Tape 5, Dec 7, 1975 (Box 34, Cassette 1696)
    - Hyman Lumer, Lectures on Multinationals and Zionism. Tape 1, Dec 9, 1975 (Box 35, Cassette 2881)
    - Hyman Lumer, Lecture on Zionism. Tape 2, Dec 9, 1975 (Box 35, Cassette 2884)
    - Hyman Lumer, Monetary Crisis, Dec 10, 1975 (Box 35, Cassette 2886)
    - Gus Hall, Fourth Stage of General Crisis, Dec 11, 1975 (Box 35, Cassette 2887)
    - Gus Hall, Opportunism, Dec 11, 1975 (Box 35, Cassette 2888)
    - Gus Hall, Opportunism, Dec 11, 1975 (Box 35, Cassette 2889)
    - Gus Hall, Opportunism. Tape 3, Dec 11, 1975 (Box 35, Cassette 2890)
    - Gus Hall, Opportunism. Tape 4, Dec 11, 1975 (Box 35, Cassette 2891)
    - Gus Hall, Opportunism. Tape 5, Dec 11, 1975 (Box 35, Cassette 2892)
    - Victor Perlo, Economic Falsifiers. Tape 2, Dec 15, 1975 (Box 59, Cassette 962)
    - Henry Winston, Ideological Problems, Dec 16, 1975 (Box 59, Cassette 1036)
    - Daniel Rubin, Seminar on the Communist Party, USA. Tape 1, Dec 18, 1975 (Box 59, Cassette 951)
    - Daniel Rubin, Seminar on the Communist Party, USA. Tape 2, Dec 18, 1975 (Box 59, Cassette 950)
    - Daniel Rubin, Seminar on the Communist Party, USA. Tape 3, Dec 18, 1975 (Box 59, Cassette 949)
    - Daniel Rubin, Seminar on the Communist Party, USA. Tape 4, Dec 18, 1975 (Box 59, Cassette 948)
    - Daniel Rubin, Seminar on the Communist Party, USA. Tape 5, Dec 18, 1975 (Box 59, Cassette 947)
    - Daniel Rubin, Seminar on the Communist Party, USA. Tape 6, Dec 18, 1975 (Box 35, Cassette 2893)
    - Daniel Rubin, Seminar on the Communist Party, USA. Tape 7, Dec 19, 1975 (Box 35, Cassette 2894)
    - Daniel Rubin, Seminar on the Communist Party, USA. Tape 8, Dec 19, 1975 (Box 35, Cassette 2895)
    - Daniel Rubin, Seminar on the Communist Party, USA. Tape 9, Dec 19, 1975 (Box 35, Cassette 2896)
    - Daniel Rubin, Seminar on the Communist Party, USA. Tape 10, Dec 19, 1975 (Box 35, Cassette 2897)
    - Daniel Rubin, Seminar on the Communist Party, USA. Tape 11, Dec 19, 1975 (Box 35, Cassette 2898)
    - 1976 Election Campaign Issues. Jarvis Tyner, Interview by Jill Furillo / Gus Hall, Interviewed by James Steele, 2.0 items 1 Access CD and original vinyl record (Box 32, Cassette 4990, Box 84)
    - 1976 Election Campaign Issues. Jarvis Tyner, on the Crisis of the Cities, Racism, Peace and National Liberation and Democracy [Note: This is a 33 1/3 vinyl recording.] (Box 32, Cassette 4991)